It's my life, it's your life, fighting for
tomorrow. Go catch what you really want.
I want more, anyone more,
come on, open up the door.
It's my life, it's your life, run
like a wind, jump high, yeah, yeah.
I know you're strong, believe
you can achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going. I'll not stay.
Let's do it again, you
know what I mean, baby.
No one can make my dream come true.
Don't you feel it? I
really don't know what is.
Something is testing me every day.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away.
I know I never wanna come back here.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away. The great
end of the unknown rules.
Standing up, blowing up.
My dream is getting wilder.
I'm not afraid, beat me, hit me.
I will never turn around.
Another day, another chance.
You know it's never too late.
If I can do it, so can you. Only without.
It's my life, it's your life.
Party for tomorrow. Go
get what you really want.
I want more, anyone more,
come on, open up the door.
It's my life. It's your life.
Run like a wind, jump high, yeah, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Believe you can achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going. Roaring.
It's my life, it's your life.
Fighting for your eyes that
I want, but your weary ones.
I want more, and you want more.
Come on, open up the gate.
It's my life. It's your life.
Shine like a star to be good, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Just that you can't achieve your best.
Let's keep on going. Out of day.
You make my day every day.
Cora, he has nothing to gain from
someone who only longs for destruction.
He's above that.
So you leave him the hell alone,
because Law is finally free now.
I still haven't been able to
fulfill your hopes for me,
but that's what I'm here to settle.
Vroom!
I've finally stopped, Doflamingo.
What do you make of Monkey D.
Luffy?
I have to ask you.
You were once a celestial dragon.
You must have something
interesting to say.
Shamble!
What do you make of the will of D?
Why should I indulge you?
That's none of your concern.
You think that this is his fate? Huh?
That Straw Hat was led here?
My divine blood enticed
him to come and kill me,
a bunch of nonsense.
One more thing; those who fear the inheritors
of d have given them another title.
Sworn enemy of gods, I'm also a d.
Can you update me on the situation, Viola?
Sadly, things are not
going well at the palace.
Straw Hat has been knocked below.
Law is struggling against Doflamingo.
Still, that is not the only battle.
There are two more.
In addition to the clashes on
the plateau and at the palace,
there are also battles
near the statue of Pika.
and at the Smile Factory.
The fire is spreading!
Don't do it!
Try to restrain them!
Hurry!
Their victims keep filing up.
We must end this.
Viola...
We defeated some of the executives, right?
So how many of them are left?
Quite a few, I'm afraid.
As I mentioned, this Mile Factory
is one of the major battlefields.
And it's still protected by the
free-swimming man, Senor Pink.
And there's a top executive
fighting on the giant statue.
The stone assimilation man, Pika.
And then of course there's the center of
our struggle on the top
level of the plateau.
There lies the despot king and string man.
With him is
his chief of
staff the mucus man treble.
In the sunflower field directly below the
palace there's the hero of the coliseum.
known as the Flag Man, Diamante.
Beneath them, on the third level,
is the Rupture Man, Gladius.
There are four executives
on the second level.
The Half-Fighting Fish Fishman, Tellinger.
The Geo-Fist Master, Lao-G.
The superweight man.
Mach Vice.
And the full body weapon.
Baby 5.
Altogether that's 10 executives to face.
Wait, did you?
That breeze is hurtin' my tear ducts, man!
Wow, so hard-boiled!
But these battles are wearing on.
And many of the fighters
are already injured.
So the end of this battle
may be close at hand.
You're a real pain.
Army Bandera.
Ground. What's happening?
Like that?
I can even make the ground ripple.
Seems hard to stand with one leg.
And clutch.
I
Know you're worried about your friends.
I can handle this place.
Oh, are you sure?
Yeah, go on
Thanks.
Now piano!
Fools.
Such feeble attacks.
Almost put me to sleep.
En garde, Gladius!
Hmm.
Destruction cannon!
You missed me!
Ten-ton!
Freeze!
You do want me, don't you?
We're on our way!
Stay strong, princess!
You all right, ma 'am? Yes.
You showed up just in time.
Better get someplace safe.
Hurry.
Don't know where it is safe, really.
If Luffy and Law cannot stop Doflamingo,
the people in the Birdcage
will never be freed.
The fate of the kingdom is in the
hands of two pirates and that's it?
You're a thief.
You have a hidden name.
And you're destined to
come here and defeat me.
Is that what you're trying to say?
Do you think you can stop me
because of some letter in your name?
That you're the sworn enemy
of the gods, driven by fate.
That's rubbish!
A legend!
Just a lie!
Whoa, Kofi!
Be careful!
You're in range of his power right now!
No!
Injection!
Shot!
Karoo knew that it would take more
than a measly D to defeat you.
And yet, when I learned the truth,
my fate changed all the same.
My name was the Catalyst.
listen I'm only here because
Cora was too kind-hearted to
pull the trigger that day so
now I'm going to do it for him
I don't like this one bit. Now room
I'm so disappointed in you.
I can't iterate that enough.
Tucked!
Don't be!
The tower's mine!
I did us!
They're good!
Spiderweb.
Stumples!
These pathetic attacks of yours
are degrading to both of us.
You think you can win with guts alone.
Since when did you become so
sentimental?
I'm afraid you're not looking
at the big picture here.
You've spent your whole life getting
hung up on meaningless little details.
That's why you've never
been able to seize the
moment law.
Worrying about other people's pain
is a sign of being small-minded.
It only leads to self-destruction.
Despite this failure, you'd be perfectly
capable of killing me if you wanted to.
Assuming you stuck to the plan and
started a fight between Kaido and I,
there's plenty of ways to take out someone
stronger than you, if you're smart.
But you weren't smart at all,
instead you were emotional.
And the moment you decided you had to
avenge Corazon with your own two hands,
you condemned yourself to certain death.
All this talk reminds me.
Do you remember that secret message?
It's not a trick.
If a marine sees this, they would
know exactly what to do with it.
A faraway kingdom called Dressrosa.
I don't get it.
I don't know who gave this
to you, but I'm grateful.
I'll take good care of
this, so don't you worry.
Corazon did a splendid job of
undermining me to save this kingdom.
Everything was going to work
out fine until you blew it.
That face says you do remember,
and it must sting, too.
You're responsible for
Corazon's death as much as me.
Imagine how history might have changed.
Every tragedy that befell this
kingdom could have been avoided.
If only you delivered that message.
Even you don't believe that.
Didn't lose your cool this
time. You're learning.
And yes, you're right.
Even with that message,
I would have found a way.
No matter what, the throne
would still have been mine.
That means Korra's own
sacrifice was meaningless.
The effort he put forth was meaningless.
The only one who can decide that is me.
Everything that I do until I
die Is a part of Korra's legacy.
Well is that so?
Why that almost brings a
tear to your eye, doesn't it?
But it's true, everything
that's done for better or worse.
Becomes a part of your
legacy etched in stone.
Like when you ate the
op-op fruit and ran away.
Or when you bared your
fangs at me on Punk Hazard.
Or when you came here and
challenged me in my own kingdom.
That was a good one, doofy!
Nothing beats the good old Sixth!
Maybe you were influenced by the other D.
But as I said, everything that's
happened is etched in stone now.
There's no changing the truth.
And that's why I forgive you.
Like I forgave my father
and forgave my brother.
That is to say, in death.
Nothing beats a lead bullet.
For a proper execution, I say.
Let's go, Fee's double.
Bingo.
It's time to fight.
He did it.
This is awful.
He got all busted up.
I suppose the cage was
a bit too small, huh?
I should have known you
wouldn't be so easy to contain.
Bellamy!
That's enough!
Mingo, come on!
Let Bellamy go!
He's gonna die!
Oh, I didn't realize he was still alive.
Well, okay.
Bellamy!
Bellamy! Flamingo!
Fine, Bellamy.
I've had my fun.
You're free from me now.
Just like you've always been, right?
Where are you from?
All of us used to live in Ortiz.
That's a wealthy city.
What's your problem with it?
It's boring as hell!
I hate that place!
I think the Don Quixote family
is the bride of the north blue.
We want to be a real pirate
crew one just like you guys!
We're not like those other pirates out
there with their heads in the clouds.
We see things your way
I'll let you use our jolly Roger.
That's what you want.
Oh, fee
Catch is if you're ever defeated.
You'll have to give it up.
You got it.
Oh, right
I don't need weaklings as my subordinates.
Don't worry, I won't lose to anyone!
Hey! Bellamy!
Are you hanging in there?
I mean, I know you're not great!
Thing is, the time when pirates
dreamt about the future is over!
I've eaten a cursed fruit too, and
you don't stand a chance against me!
Spring!
Haki!
For starters, I saw the
Sky Island just like you.
I lost all my crewmates on that trip,
But it turned my view of
the world upside down.
I'm not going to hold a
grudge against you anymore.
Either way, I'm done laughing at you.
You okay?
You have changed, Bellamy.
Hey, don't push yourself.
Just rest for a sec.
So Joker is ordering me
to murder Straw Hat now?
Dolphy's a generous leader.
Even though you lost the tournament,
he's giving you one more
chance to redeem yourself.
You should be happy your task is so easy.
Well,
if you're standing there
and not murdering Straw Hat,
then I say you're not busy enough.
You need me to give you a hand?
Huh, weird. An earthquake.
You really want me to spell
it out for you? All right?
Your purpose has never
been the same as mine.
I can't do it!
You're my friend!
Hey, Bellamy.
I'm sorry.
I gotta leave you here for now.
I'm real worried about Traffy.
The real Mingo and Snot Guy are up there.
They're too strong.
He needs my help.
I'll give Mingo an extra kick
in the ass for you, okay?
Hold on.
You remember this technique?
It's been a while.
Okay, you ready?
Spring Hopper!
Let's go!
You got stronger since last
time, but I got stronger too!
You want to see destructive power?
I'm taking this to the max!
You're finally free!
Now cut it out before you die!
Pathetic!
Stop showing mercy to your enemy!
I know I'm pitiful!
I know I looked up to the wrong man!
I don't need to hear it from you!
Nah.
That's for the victor to decide.
This pitiful worm,
crawled here just to die.
Isn't that right, Bellamy?
But I made my choice.
I can't turn on him just because
I didn't get what I wanted.
If I don't see this through to the
end, then I'll be worse than a failure.
I'll be a complete disgrace.
I have to hold on to something.
Even a loser like me has some dignity.
See?
This will be my final battle, Straw Hat!
See it through to the end with me!